Minot, Samuel Lawrence, 1826-1853. Letters to John Sherman Minot (MS Am 1106): Guide.
Letters to John Sherman Minot,
1845-1847.
Houghton Library, Harvard College Library, Harvard University
MS Am 1106
Minot, Samuel Lawrence, 1826-1853.
1 box (.5 linear ft.)
Letters from Phillips Academy student Samuel Lawrence Minot to his brother John living in Belgrade, Maine.
Recat. from Cl 9886.
Bequest of Mrs. G. Reed Kelly; received: 1938.
Arranged chronologically.
Samuel Minot's letters to his brother John chiefly describe his studies at Phillips Academy in Andover, Massachusetts. He also discusses travels in New England, and his political support of the Whig Party and of the abolition of slavery in New Hampshire.
- Minot, Samuel Lawrence, 1826-1853. A.L.s. to John Sherman Minot; Andover, Mass., 14 Jan 1845., (1); 1s.(2p.)
- Minot, Samuel Lawrence, 1826-1853. A.L.s. to John Sherman Minot; Manchester, N.H., 6 Mar 1845., (2); 1s.(3p.)
- Minot, Samuel Lawrence, 1826-1853. A.L.s. to John Sherman Minot; Manchester, N.H., 24 May 1845., (3); 1s.(3p.)
- Minot, Samuel Lawrence, 1826-1853. A.L.s. to John Sherman Minot; Manchester, N.H., 14 Jun 1845., (4); 1s.(3p.)
- Minot, Samuel Lawrence, 1826-1853. A.L.s. to John Sherman Minot; Manchester, N.H., 3 Sep 1845., (5); 1s.(3p.)
- Minot, Samuel Lawrence, 1826-1853. A.L.s. to John Sherman Minot; Andover, Mass., 9 Oct 1845., (6); 1s.(4p.)
- Minot, Samuel Lawrence, 1826-1853. A.L.s. to John Sherman Minot; Manchester, N.H., 12 Dec 1845., (7); 1s.(2p.)
- Minot, Samuel Lawrence, 1826-1853. A.L.s. to John Sherman Minot; Andover, Mass., 16 Feb 1846., (8); 1s.(3p.)
- Minot, Samuel Lawrence, 1826-1853. A.L.s. to John Sherman Minot; Andover, Mass., 18 Mar 1846., (9); 1s.(3p.)
- Minot, Samuel Lawrence, 1826-1853. A.L.s. to John Sherman Minot; Andover, Mass., 22 Apr 1846., (10); 1s.(2p.)
- Minot, Samuel Lawrence, 1826-1853. A.L.s. to John Sherman Minot; Andover, Mass., 15 Jul 1846., (11); 1s.(3p.)
- Minot, Samuel Lawrence, 1826-1853. A.L.s. to John Sherman Minot; Andover, Mass., 9 Sep 1846., (12); 1s.(3p.)
- Minot, Samuel Lawrence, 1826-1853. A.L.s. to John Sherman Minot; Andover, Mass., 23 Nov 1846., (13); 1s.(3p.)
- Minot, Samuel Lawrence, 1826-1853. A.L.s. to John Sherman Minot; Andover, Mass., 10 Feb 1847., (14); 1s.(4p.)
- Minot, Samuel Lawrence, 1826-1853. A.L.s. to John Sherman Minot; Andover, Mass., 25 Apr 1847., (15); 1s.(4p.)
- Minot, Samuel Lawrence, 1826-1853. A.L.s. to John Sherman Minot; Andover, Mass., 3 Jul 1847., (16); 1s.(4p.)
- Minot, Samuel Lawrence, 1826-1853. A.L.s. to John Sherman Minot; Andover, Mass., 16 Jul 1847., (17); 1s.(2p.)
- Minot, Samuel Lawrence, 1826-1853. A.L.s. to John Sherman Minot; Manchester, N.H., 8 Aug 1847., (18); 1s.(2p.)
- Minot, Samuel Lawrence, 1826-1853. A.L.s. to John Sherman Minot; Manchester, N.H., 28 Aug 1847., (19); 1s.(3p.)